Seino, Galgal Channel, GO!
We are now at a hotel in Osaka.
Today I'd like to talk about the hotel off-topic.
Please take a look.
Let's have a doughnut.
These are doughnuts.
Doughnuts, Kentucky, and a few other things.
This is not the only dinner I had for dinner.
But it was close by, so I stopped by and bought some.
This is enough food for 8 people.
Maybe one of the members will come and get it while we're shooting the video.
I'm sure the members will come and get it while we're shooting the video.
I'll be right there. Let's eat!
Cheers!
Today I'm taking pictures after the release event at Aeon Mall Kisogawa Sunday on May 5th in Osaka.
Children's Day?
Yes, it was!
It was Children's Day!
I ordered a burger at Kentucky for the first time!
I told you that, didn't I?
Yeah?
Chicken Hill.
I want to try it.
One more time.
Oh, I changed.
I'm changing by myself.
That's right.
I wasn't touching you.
I think I'll go without touching you.
Burger.
Looks good.
I think I've had one of those.
You have?
It's kind of good.
I've heard it's good.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
I feel like it's been a while since I've had it.
It's delicious.
I knew it was different.
It's totally different from a chicken burger from a hamburger shop.
Chicken from a hamburger shop.
I really wanted to prepare takoyaki or something.
I wanted to prepare something like takoyaki.
We were going to have something from Osaka, but...
But we got close to the restaurant.
We just ordered whatever we wanted.
It's really off-topic.
Off-topic.
How about I show you my room?
You just said "pee.
Pee is for this.
Headphones.
Look at these headphones.
Bunny bread.
The manager bought this for lunch at Lily's today.
Hey!
I heard it's that one.
Kashi-bun!
They say it's egg and dairy free!
It's good for you, right?
It's something, isn't it?
Even for kids with allergies.
There's something about Kashi-bun.
I've got someone's fries here, and I don't want to eat them.
I don't want to eat them.
If you don't come in and order a drink or something...
It'll melt.
I might melt.
Here.
Nice fight.
Guess what.
Ready?
All right.
Yooka.
Yooka-kira's
This thump
Akidaruma Kuro
You're so loud.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
Yoo-hoo!
Welcome home!
You must be Yooka's god.
I'm back!
Hey, what's up?
Knock-knock!
It's like "kon-kon-kon!
First one to arrive!
Yes, first!
If you'd like to introduce yourself...
Hello!
Kira Yamaguchi
First-time visitor, first-time visitor...
First time seeing you.
Yes
Yes, chicken.
I'll share with Ms. Ogawa.Separate with Mr. Ogawa
Original
Wow.
Amazing!
4 pieces
Can you share this?
You can't split this?
I don't have chopsticks.
Well, have fun!
Okay, okay.
Bye bye.
Good night.
See you later.
Sweet Neck of Cheese
Here you go.
[Hajime Shacho ending]
I can't see.
It smells so good!
It was Yooka.
And from there...
It sounded like "yooka yooka.
Yeah, it's like a wall.
You just said snowman.
That was Hinachi.
Hinachi did.
That's why.
In this area.
With the members...
You too...
I have to introduce myself first.
I'm Yooka.
Good work, Ram.
Coming this way?
What?
Are you early?
Is no one expected?
Did someone come?
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Harada Toa from Girls Girls Girls.
Hello.
Did you come barefoot?
I'm all alone.
And you're the one who changed clothes.
Thanks for the ram, Toa.
Thank you very much.
Some impressions.
I was allowed to wear different outfits from my personal clothes,
It was fun.
What is the theme of Toa?
When you are the hero of a movie.
When I was the main character of the movie.
The way he walks.
The way I walk.
I was made to smile as the main character.
Like a doll.
It looked good on me.
Thank you very much.
I will do my best.
I don't eat kentaki.
You don't usually eat?
Why the injury?
I don't usually eat kentaki.
I have a weak stomach.
I don't like fatty meat.
When we go out for barbeque together,
You're taking it easy.
I am totally fine.
I'm sleepy to try yakiniku.
Where do you want to go?
Sushi.
I was thinking sushi.
What kind of prefecture?
Just the standard stuff.
A high-end chain restaurant.
The surroundings are nice.
There's staff.
Or a dinner party.
Go to Kaiten Sushi.
Girls conveyor belt sushi.
All of them.
Amazing.
Conveyor belt sushi going on next time.
Please do.
Enjoy.
Thank you very much.
Ah!
My stomach hurts.
Cosmo is doing inky.
Ah, se-ee!
Eh, Momo-san, Momo-san.
Se-no!
Yankachina
Se-no
Momochan
Momo yapeach orchard
Momoyan
And he's posing.
I wonder if I'm in the right frame of mind.
I don't know if I caught it.
I don't think so.
Okay, bye.
I did the inky thing.
I can't take this with me.
I'm gonna go try one time.
You should try it.
Whenever you're ready.
Introduce yourself.
I'm 18 years old.
I'm in my first year of work.
My name is Momoka Sumitari
I'm glad to see you here.
I said I'd introduce myself to everyone who's been here so far.
Everyone only says their name.
I'm 18 years old
I'm scared, scared
I don't know what to do.
I'll be here today.
I'll still be here tomorrow
We met yesterday.
Now we're meeting.
Seriously.
Welcome.
That's great.
Momochan, you wanna come here?
Can I come in the middle?
Momo, but this is the smallest room.
Wait, wait. Last?
Last.
Introduce yourself.
Hi, Momo.
I did a good thing.
Not too much, is it?
But it's not like I've ever introduced myself before.
Pop Talent.
That's not how you just introduced yourself.
Let's do it again.
Hello, hello.
I'm Yuzu.
It's a hotel, isn't it?
It's a hotel.
I guess so.
I was eating the most before I knew it.
That's right.
We're off-talking at the hotel.
Not at home,
I'm not at home, but I'm doing the hotel routine.
Lately, I've been able to turn on the TV.
I've started to turn on the TV.
YouTube
I can now turn on YouTube.
There are a lot of things that can be connected.
Mirroring and so on.
There's one that allows you to watch YouTube, Abema, etc.
I might check it out first.
There's one for today.
YouTube?
Yes, there is Abema.
I don't usually turn on TV.
But I'll bring my
I'll bring my own pajamas, for sure.
Yeah.
I did that when I was 20.
I'm going to put out TikTok in three colors.
Right this way.
Hey, Gen.
You mean you can't sleep?
Yeah.
Let me show you.
He's introducing me. If you're so kind.
Last time we saw you, you were in green.
Green.
Green with a purple top.
It's purple.
This one's purple.
This one.
It's legendary.
Um...
Can I show you something?
Camisole. Camisole.
Today.
Oh, here.
Snoopy.
Isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
But you know what? Snoopy's...
The pink character.
Which one of these two are you getting?
That's why I want it.
I want it.
I want it
I want it! I want it!
It's so cute!He's so cute.
I'm really into baseball.
That's why I watch Abema on a TV with a disposable screen.
It's easier to watch.
I sacrifice a lot of sleep to watch baseball games.
Early in the morning.
Since he's hooked on baseball, he's even more lively.
Every day.
I think sports are great, and not just baseball.
My dad used to play baseball.
I used to play.
When I was a student or an adult, it was like a hobby.
I have a favorite team because of that.
Minami's father also likes baseball.
So you played?
Not only baseball. Quite a lot of things?
And, um, he went to see a baseball game today.
He sent me that video on the family line. So you know about soccer, too?
Yes, I do. She also watches rugby.
Soccer girl? Yeah. Legends.
Legendary MVP. No, it's not like that. I can't play soccer if I really know how to exercise.
Since then? Yes, I couldn't do it from then, but it was the time when Nadesico Japan won the championship.
The whole world was excited. The world was hot.
And they were handing out flyers in front of the school, so I thought I'd go and see if I could find some free time.
You mean before you started dancing?
From the third grade to the sixth or fifth grade, so for a few years I was in the club thing.
So I was in a club for a few years, and there was a camp. The same club. There were cages in various places.
What kind of cages? Yes, yes, yes. I participated in it, and I won MVP at that camp.
But you know what, I was so excited that I used my hand by mistake in this soccer game.
I mean, really? Spouter would get really mad at me if I did that.
Soccer is a game. I was at the point where I said, "Don't play soccer," and yet I won the MVP award.
The reason is because his greeting was really good.
I feel like it's the way of EXPG students.
I already know how to be an EXPG student even before the event starts.
Because I really don't do anything. I'm really just running around the edge of the court.
I really can't imagine. I won the MVP for that.
You didn't play much in terms of soccer skills, but did you enjoy it? Did you enjoy playing soccer?
Yes, I did. I have fond memories of it. The ballet?
Ballet?
This ballet?
Wait, wait, wait.
That was a little stupid.
Why are you talking about yourself?
He was tap dancing.
You're messing with me.
Not just tap dancing.
It's not just tap dancing.
I was in a school.
The solo teacher was pretty good.
They were doing all kinds of genres
Jazz, lip-op, and tap ballet.
and tap ballet.
I took the all-you-can-pay course
I took all kinds of courses.
I didn't take the tap course first.
But
I was the only one taking lessons.
I don't have a girls' school.
Teach me.
They always explain it to me.
Here.
I don't know what it is, but...
Just before we go on stage.
Right before we go on stage.
I always start the tap workshop in the sleeve.
I wonder why.
Maybe it's the floor.
Chitty-chitty.
You mean "chan-chan"?
Chan-chan.
Ta-da!
Why?
You're messing with me, aren't you?
You said the drinks were good.
You didn't buy any.
Kentucky and...
I don't think I'd like to drink with Miss D's.
I thought Kentucky would be good with it.
I don't know.
What would go with it?
If it's alcohol.
Comments
Galgal Channel
Sake recommendations
It's a bit of a surprise, isn't it?
First-timers.
Clea, you're almost there.
We're almost there.
But, you know, the Galgal Channel...
You've been doing this for quite a while, right?
Yes, we have.
We've been doing the same kind of projects.
But I wonder...
What do you like among them?
I'd like to know.
Please ask.
Please do.
Mmmmmm!
I wish we could get to 50,000 subscribers, but we're at 4.7.
I just looked at it and I'm wondering what people like... dancing, I guess.
I thought we should do something that would please them as much as possible, and I saw that dance is growing more.We thought it would be good to make people as happy as possible, so we looked at it and saw that the dancing was growing.
Can I eat this? And maybe you'd like to see some outside projects.
I've been consciously trying to cool down a bit lately.
I'll eat it in my room. I'll eat it in my room, please.
If they find out, they'll play with the leader. Animals? I don't have anything that interesting.
I don't have anything interesting to say about that. Claire doesn't have to say anything about that. Until she buys a lion.
I'd like to be born in a place where lions are a thing of the afterlife.
I'd like to be born in a place like that... and start doing more environmental work abroad... and get to know people over there.
In this way...
I'd like to be...
I want to be like this.
That's what I said!
He's really going to be a lion.
He's going to be a lion.
If you're going to end up a lion, just say you want to be one.
That's not it.
I'm talking about...
I've done a lot of work on the environment and all that.
I want to be a lion.
Well, then, Rice, wouldn't it be better to be a lion from the start?
Not a human.
Oh, no...
Rice... what a physique!
It's difficult.
Yes, it is.
I'm sorry, I just...
Time to end this.
Alone.
If you're the type...
Okay, well, what I'm trying to say is...
What do I do now, there's two of us?
What am I gonna do? - Existing people.
You're gonna be an existing person.
That's impossible.
Miho Imada.
I see.
You're not going to put it on, are you?
The other one is Kanon Fujii.
So you want to be in show business in your next life?
I'd like to be a pretty person.
Cute, you mean.
That's good enough.
I want to be beautiful.
I hope so.
I hope so, even if I'm born again.
I'll be born again. Please take care of me.
Miho Imada.
I hope you can be.
I want to be human in the first place.
I understand.
I like dogs and cats.
I like dogs and cats, but I don't want to be one of them, I want to be the one who admires them.
I used to say I wanted to be a bird.
I used to say I wanted to be a bird, but I wanted to fly.
I want to eat bugs and stuff.
But you know... you're Claire.
You can't eat bugs because you're Claire.
She might have changed her mind.
When you become a bird...
But I think it's human nature to eat good food.
Claire has always been famous.
Eating good food is the best part of being human.
Only humans can cook.
Mii is like that.
She has feelings
Like only humans can express them.
Even dogs express themselves.
It happens sometimes.
What do you mean?
Only humans can communicate.
But that's just it.
Minami and humans are the only ones who can communicate.
That's true.
Is there anything else you'd like to do in my room?
Not particularly. It's sad.
Nothing in particular. Nothing in particular.
Nothing in particular. Okay, I'm gonna tear it down later.
I'm going to go home to my room after this. I'm going to go home quietly. It's a release event tomorrow.
Yeah, and the day after tomorrow, too, if you don't want to stay up too late.
I'll take a good night's rest.
So, any feedback?
Yeah, it was fun.
What did you think?
It was great.
Do you have any impressions?
It was fun!
So thank you for watching!
If you liked this video, please subscribe to the channel and leave a comment!
Bye bye bye.